[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
One hundred pesos
to become part of Anino.
I'll think about it.
What I don't understand, Pops,
is why you're so impressed
with him.
Out of all our members,
he's the weakest.
- Who left this?
- No one, Gabo.
Victor Zafra alias "Tiger."
Mr. Chan will have
a transaction,
and it's likely
with Victor Zafra.
This is our mission.
We have to keep Mr. Chan
under surveillance
from his jewelry store
until he leaves.
We will follow him anywhere
because he's our lead to where
the transaction will take place.
If you're watching this video...
...it means you've accepted
the mission.
Tiger leads the largest gold
smuggling operations
in the country.
Your mission, Gabo, is
to bring us Victor Zafra
dead or alive.
[DOORS OPENING, CREAKING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Lucas.
Tomorrow...
Come with me
when I meet with Mr. Chan.
Papa is right.
You have to learn the business
at an early age.
[LUCAS INHALES DEEPLY]
Wait.
How--
- How are you? Are you okay?
- I'm fine, Victor.
I can actually fight against
Stallone and Harris.
I just let them beat me.
I know you can win against them.
I know you can,
but I'm your older brother.
You can't stop me from
protecting you against anyone.
Thank you, brother.
But I am no longer a child.
I can handle myself.
And I'll prove that to you.
[PATTING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[KAREN] Oh.
Sam!
It's good you were able
to handle Ma'am Pia.
It wasn't obvious
that you were nervous.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm!
Gosh, I was so nervous.
My heart was pounding so fast.
I just gathered the courage
to speak.
But I also just told myself
this isn't for Ma'am Pia.
This is for our country.
I know that,
that's why you're my idol.
But, you know,
I was actually shaking earlier.
- You were shaking in fear?
- No.
I was shaking in frustration,
in anger!
Ma'am Pia's so frustrating!
She keeps looking
for gaps and shortcomings,
and she'll turn it
into a huge issue!
She's so annoying.
I wanted to squeeze her!
Calm down.
You know we're not doing this
to ask for praise, right?
Or to get recognition
in the NCIA.
We're doing this
to lessen the number
of criminals in this country.
[SAM BREATHES DEEPLY]
That includes that annoying man.
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA"
BY JUAN KARLOS PLAYING]
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, okay.
I'll take note of that.
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA" CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
- "Victor "Tiger" Zafra"
- [PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
- [GABO SCREAMS]
- [TEKLA AND FRIENDS SHRIEK]
- Ow! Ow! Ow!
- What the hell, Gabo?!
It's just us! Your friends!
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- My heart...
- You almost stabbed me!
What are you doing here?
Where the hell were you?!
You just disappeared!
We were so worried!
[TOLITS] Uh, Gabo?
A-Are you still mad at us?
I'm so sorry for what I said.
I'm not mad anymore.
Forget about it.
Okay, come in.
[BINOY] Put that machete away!
[TEKLA]
Gosh, why do you have that?
- You scared us.
- You almost hit me, Gabo!
[BINOY CLEARS THROAT]
What's that? A school project?
[MUSIC FADES]
When we went back to the bar
to get our clothes,
the owner was so furious
because of what you did
to their customers.
If we show up there again,
they said they'd press charges.
Where were you anyway, Gabo?
Something happened.
- I was abducted.
- Huh?
- Huh?!
- What?!
Wh-Who?!
I don't know them.
But I remember seeing them
in prison.
Why did they abduct you?
And how did you get away?
It's a long story.
I'll tell you everything later.
Earlier, while I was alone here,
someone knocked on the door.
They left this parcel outside.
What's inside?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
A mission.
It's a job for me.
Mission? What kind of mission?
Hunting down people
who have broken the law.
They want you to
hunt people down?
I've seen that in foreign films!
What's it called? Mission...
Just like James Bond!
- He's like James Bond!
- James Bond?
Mission Is Possible?!
You're wrong!
He's more like Agent 00!
Don't make things up.
I've never heard of Agent 00.
Don't you know Weng Weng?
The short guy?
He's the Philippines'
James Bond.
He uses an umbrella
to jump over buildings.
Your James Bond
doesn't hold a candle to him.
Oh, I remember now.
That's a really old show.
- Back in your days, right?
- Yeah.
Wow, Gabo!
You've really come so far!
You're now a secret agent
hunting down outlaws!
What a glow-up!
Yeah, that's basically
what my job is going to be.
That's so cool!
Gabo, can you recommend us
to your bosses?
- We can go on missions, too.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh... [CLEARS THROAT]
How much are we talking?
One hundred thousand pesos.
- One hundred thousand?!
- One hundred thousand?
- Wow, that's a huge amount.
- A hundred thousand?
Gabo, how will we split the pay
if we find those men?
Fifty percent will go to me.
You can share
the other 50 percent.
- That's if you'll help me.
- Oh! I'm definitely in, Gabo.
I'd rather be a secret agent
than be unemployed.
Hey, we're in too.
Gabo, count us in.
[TOLITS] Count us in, too!
We're in!
I'm sure you can use our help.
[BINOY] So, we're settled?
Okay.
If you're up for the job,
let's search for this man
tomorrow.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[FOOTSTEPS SHUFFLING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Sam!
[CLEARS THROAT] Sam, Sam!
[CLEARS THROAT] Sam...
[CREAKS]
Congrats, Sam.
Congrats for what?
For the briefing earlier?
Don't we do those normally?
Oh, no, no.
Congrats because, um...
I know that our mission
is going to be successful.
I can already see it!
[CHUCKLES] Wow.
So you have a super power, huh?
Oh, you!
[SQUEALING] Didn't know
you have a funny bone!
I'm glad I could bring out
this side of you.
Oh, but on our mission,
I'll stick to you always.
I'll be your knight
in shining armor.
Because you don't know
what'll happen on our mission.
Maybe someone
will mess with you.
Or you could be kissed
randomly again!
I'll hit those bastards
with my uppercut!
- Right? You know I can!
- [CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
You need my protection, Sam.
You know what, I don't need
your protection.
Should those things
happen to me again,
I'll slap them back to back.
I hope your super powers
saw that one coming.
[SQUEALING MOCKINGLY]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[MAX] Dad, so many people
got injured in Ginintuang Lupa.
Good thing the mayor's men
arrived on time
to put a stop to the demolition.
This won't end today.
There will be more men
for the next demolition
in Ginintuang Lupa.
[ISOBEL] Um...
Whatever the kind of solution
you'll come up with,
just make sure that our family
won't be involved physically.
- [ISOBEL BREATHES DEEPLY]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- Sam! Let's eat.
- [ISOBEL] Oh!
[ISOBEL] Sweetie,
have you eaten yet?
[SAM] I have.
Dad.
Uh... I'll just go upstairs.
Anyway, Dad, if you ever
need anything,
the police is ready
to help, okay?
[RICARDO] And I'm telling you,
if they want this demolition
to be even bloodier,
I'll give it to them!
[RICARDO] I'll be happy
to accommodate.
[SAM, VOICE BREAKING] Uh...
Excuse me, wait a second.
The demolition was bloody?
I thought we put the operation
aside for now?
It already happened, Sam.
It just didn't push through.
Exactly. I thought we're not
going to drive them out anymore.
Why do you care about
those people so much?
[ISOBEL WHISPERING] Ricardo...
The people in Ginintuang Lupa
are nothing but trash!
All I know is that it's going
to cause us problems
if we rush them
into leaving the area.
- [CLATTERS]
- Oh my god. Enough, Ricardo.
Those good for nothings
are thugs
and are completely useless
to our society.
I'm even doing God's work
in driving those pests away!
[SAM] They might be poor,
but they're still human.
And I hope we treat them
like one!
They're living off
of my property.
They don't deserve any mercy!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
So if you don't know enough,
it's best you shut up.
[ISOBEL SOBS]
- Sam!
- [CHAIR RATTLES]
Sit down.
- [MAX] Excuse me.
- Sit down.
- Samantha!
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Sam!
- [DOOR SLAMS CLOSE]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN]
You okay?
Sam.
Dad has a point, okay?
He owns the land,
so he can do whatever he wants.
Sure, he can.
I just thought that
maybe he should pause
and think about the people.
Especially those who live there.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
[PHONE RINGING]
[MAX] Who's that?
- Well?
- No one.
Who is it?
- Come on, give it to me.
- No, no...
- Why not answer it?
- No need.
- It's not work-related.
- Come on, answer.
Ah, so it's personal.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
He's been wooing you for ages.
When will you say yes?
Why would I?
I don't have any feelings
for him.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAX] Hmm?
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, come on.
You know what they say?
- Hmm, what?
- In love,
you'll feel a hundred emotions.
Joy, excitement, nervousness...
All mixed together.
But when it comes to Seb,
there's only one thing
I feel toward him.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Annoyance.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- I know you.
He's exactly your type.
Clean, decent, formal.
Me, I like bad boys.
Don't drag it out.
He'll end up being your
boyfriend, I'm telling you.
You know, I'm not in a hurry.
Why are you pressuring me?
I'm a very beautiful woman.
There are other guys
waiting for me.
A whole lot of them.
- Hmm?
- No, just kidding.
[GIGGLES]
That was a joke?
Ah, you're into some guy,
but you're not telling me.
- Not true! Come on...
- Who is it?
- No one!
- Just tell me.
Nobody! Okay, go away now!
I still need to review my cases.
[MAX] Hmm?
What? [GIGGLES]
Just go!
If I find out something,
you'll see.
- Go with your bad boys.
- Whatever.
- Alright, good night.
- Bye.
Hmm?
[BOTH GIGGLING]
- You sure?
- Just drop it! Bye-bye!
[MAX] Poor guy.
Give him your answer!
Good night.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [CAR HORN HONKING]
[DOOR SQUEAKS CLOSE]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[SALVADOR] Hey, Oli.
What's the problem?
Where is it?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
Wait, wait, wait.
I said what's the problem?
- [BANGS TABLE]
- [INHALES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[GRUNTING]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[OLI] Salvador.
The person we interviewed
last night...
The one whose spouse was shot?
Well, what happened?
Let's present it to Boss Arnel.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Don't tell me you didn't get
the interview on record, Oli.
[ARNEL] What?! You failed
to record it, Oli?!
[SIGHS EXASPERATEDLY]
Boss...
You know the consequence
of that mistake!
Boss... Boss, have mercy!
Boss, my wife just gave birth!
I'm the only one providing
for them. Besides, boss--
Boss, I have a side chick!
I cover her internet bill, boss!
I'm the one supporting
them all, boss!
- Boss, I can't lose this job!
- Let me go--
- Stay away!
- I'm begging you!
I don't want any excuses!
If you make a mistake,
you're fired!
[SALVADOR] Boss, boss, boss.
Calm down, boss. Calm down.
Let's give him a second chance.
He's nice.
[ARNEL SIGHING]
He's in my hands, boss.
He's my responsibility.
Don't worry.
I'll fix this, boss.
I need news that
will attract viewers.
[SALVADOR]
We'll do another interview
with the victim's family.
I promise you, boss.
This will be a hit.
Everyone will see it,
and it'll be the interview
of a lifetime.
That's my promise, boss.
Just don't fire him.
Be grateful, Oli,
that Salvador came
to your rescue.
I'll give you another chance!
But I'm coming along this time.
I don't want sloppy work
on the jobs that feed
your families,
and your mistress!
Boss, someone might hear you.
That woman is hideous.
That's harsh.
I love her, and that's all
that matters.
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN DISTANCE]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[TWINKLE] Ma'am?
[DOOR OPENS]
- Ma'am?
- [SAM] Twinkle.
- Good morning.
- Please, let me help you.
- Oh no, thank you.
- Huh?
It's okay. I got it.
Why?
Well, you didn't eat last night.
You also didn't tell me
what time you were going
to wake up,
or if you'd have breakfast.
So...
I took the initiative
to check on you.
Why did you get up early today?
I need to be at the office.
I have a lot of important things
to finish.
Oh.
Ooh! Looks like you're going
to have a busy day!
That's why
you'd better head downstairs,
eat breakfast to keep you
energized throughout the day!
Right? And great timing, ma'am.
Your mother
is already downstairs.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES] I'll skip breakfast.
- I'll just say goodbye to them.
- Huh?
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, everything should be ready.
Once Ricardo gets down,
serve him
hot coffee immediately.
Oh, what else is in the kitchen?
Good morning, Mom.
- I'll get going.
- Huh?
What? You're leaving?
It's bad getting used
to skipping breakfast.
I've got things to take care of
in the office.
Oh, really?
Then tell me about it.
Have a seat.
- [CHUCKLES HESITANTLY]
- Come on.
[CHAIR DRAGS]
Now, tell me.
So, why is my youngest
always in a hurry?
We're handling a huge case
in NCIA.
It's a gold smuggling case.
This is our only chance
to catch those syndicates.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- A gold smuggling case.
Goodness, that's no joke.
Are you sure youre safe
with that?
- [RICARDO CLEARS THROAT]
- Oh!
Oh, Ricardo, your daughter here
is after a syndicate.
Sam got that after you.
Worrying about small matters
we shouldn't even
be thinking about.
The case I'm leading has been
researched by the team well.
That's why I'll be safe, Mom.
Ricardo, don't you have
anything else to say, like...
at least some advice.
Anything.
It's just another day
in the office.
When I was her age,
I had dealt
with a much more serious case.
Well, Sam...
the fact that you are the lead
in this operation--
I just want you to know that
me and your Dad
are so proud of you.
[CUTLERY CLANKS]
[RICARDO] Isobel.
Easy on boosting
your daughter's confidence.
That can get to her head.
She hasn't proven anything yet.
[MUSIC TURNS MELLOW]
[CUTLERY CLANKS]
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAM] Team,
we have been planning
for this day for a long time.
Let's do our best
to catch the target.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Yes, maam!
Let's keep our communication
lines open.
Once you see the target,
notify us immediately.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TONY] Ma'am.
the warrants for Mr. Chan
and Victor Zafra are here.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's go.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Team Leader Sam.
Get ready, okay?
Don't mess this up.
We're ready, ma'am.
Thank you for the confidence.
You can thank me later
once you've brought
the targets here.
That is,
if you can actually
bring them.
Pia.
My office. Now.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
Sam.
Team Alpha,
good luck to you.
I know you won't let
the agency down.
- Yes, sir!
Let's move!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OMENG] Pops.
Gabo took the mission.
[TOMAS] The real question is...
will he do it?
I'm sure that Gabo
will chicken out.
Let's find someone else, pops.
Give him some time.
I have strong faith
that Gabo will carry out
the mission.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNIFE SWISHES]
[RUBBER STRETCHING]
[METAL RATTLING]
[SWISHES]
[METAL RATTLING, SWISHES]
[THUDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
The patient
is in critical condition.
He needs to be
operated on immediately.
This job will be a huge help.
It won't just be for you...
it will also change
your family's life.
Your spouse is dying!
Give it your all.
Three, two, one, action!
[WAILING]
We need your help,
we don't have any money!
- [WAILING]
- We need your he--
Hey!
[NARRATOR] Two groups.
- Hey!
- That hurt!
- Are you blind?!
Am I blind? I'm huge.
How could you not see me?
Whoa, he's fiesty!
Are you underestimating us?
Two, three, four...
[SINGING] Filipinos come on
and join in!
Kung Hei Fat Choy!
[SINGING] Filipinos come on
and join in!
Kung Hei Fat Choy!
[NARRATOR] One mission.
Team.
The target is coming out.
Visuals on target.
We'll follow him.
Mr. Chan will lead us
to Tiger.
We'll follow him
and trap them there.
We need to catch Tiger.
Are you sure about the
work we are doing?
I hope we get paid well.
Our lives might be
at risk here, Gabo.
Sam. Positive.
[NARRATOR] Will they
work together...
They have millions of pesos
and gold in there!
[NARRATOR] or will they clash?
- Excuse me!
- Ouch! Ouch!
- You again?!
- What do you mean?!
You're so rude!
Hey, do you want me
to kiss you?
- Jerk!
- [GROANS] Argh!
Hey, you jerk!
Do you know that
I'm an NCIA agent?!
[ENGINE REVVS]
Catch them!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- [ENGINE REVVS]
- [TRUCK HORN BLARING]
- [CRASHES]
[NARRATOR] The King of Tondo.
[NARRATOR] We're going all out
in this clash.
[GROANS] Argh!
[METAL ROD CLANGS]
[GLASS BREAKING]